const Quizquestions = [
  {
    question: "What city does the game prominently feature?",
    choices: ["Waterdeep", "Baldur's Gate", "Neverwinter", "Luskane"],
    correctAnswer: "Baldur's Gate",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Bhaal?",
    choices: [
      "The God of Murder",
      "The God of Death",
      "The Lord of Darkness",
      "The Goddes of Darkness",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The God of Murder",
  },
  {
    question: "Which D&D edition rules does Baldur's Gate 3 adapt?",
    choices: ["Fourth Edition", "Fifth Edition", "Third Edition", "Pathfinder"],
    correctAnswer: "Fifth Edition",
  },
  {
    question: "Which character is a vampire spawn?",
    choices: ["Astarion", "Volo", "Raphael", "Luskane"],
    correctAnswer: "Astarion",
  },
  {
    question: "Which Githyanki warrior is a potential party member?",
    choices: ["Vlaakith", "Kith'rak Voss", "Lae'zel", "Orpehus"],
    correctAnswer: "Lae'zel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What affliction do the main characters share at the beginning of the game?",
    choices: [
      "Lycanthropy",
      "Mind Flayer tadpole",
      "Vampirism",
      "Curse of Strahd",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Mind Flayer tadpole",
  },
  {
    question: "Which race is not playable in Baldur's Gate 3?",
    choices: ["Tiefling", "Half-Elf", "Gnome", "Drow"],
    correctAnswer: "Gnome",
  },

  {
    question: "Which class is not available in Baldur's Gate 3?",
    choices: ["Sorcerer", "Paladin", "Monk", "Blood Hunter"],
    correctAnswer: "Blood Hunter",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the deity associated with Shadowheart, the cleric?",
    choices: ["Lolth", "Shar", "Lathander", "Selune"],
    correctAnswer: "Shar",
  },
  {
    question: "What is a roll?",
    choices: [
      "A script with relevant player information",
      "A bonus action",
      "A performance check",
      "A baked good, worth 1 Camp Supply",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A performance check",
  },
];

export default Quizquestions;
